RG 005:035, Office of the Governor: Thomas J. Meskill (1971-1975)
Connecticut State Library
- Series 7. Agency Files, 1971-1975
  - Mental Health Department (Box A-817)
    - Subject Files (Box A-819)
      - Thank You Letter to Members of Advisory Boards and Superintendents (Box A-820)
      - Mental Health Printed Letter (Box A-820)
      - Milford Academy Speech (Box A-820)
      - New Britain Child Guidance (Box A-820)
      - News Releases (Box A-820)
      - Norwich Hospital (Box A-820)
      - Personnel (Box A-820)
      - Personnel Rpts. (Box A-820)
      - Pamphlets, Bulletins, Info., etc. (Box A-820)
      - Public Works Projects (Box A-820)
      - Ribicoff Research Center (Box A-821)
      - Revenue Sharing (Box A-821)
      - Security Treatment Audit Report (Box A-821)
      - Security Treatment Center, 2 folders (Box A-821)
      - South Central Mental Health Region (Box A-821)
      - Speaking Engagements (Box A-821)
      - State Board of Mental Health (Box A-821)
      - Steering Committee Final Report (Box A-821)
      - Undercliff (Box A-821)
      - U.S. District Court – District of Conn. (Box A-821)
      - Westbrook Mental Health Day Center (Box A-821)
      - Wheeler Affiliates (Box A-821)
      - Wheeler Affiliates – Letter, 1973 September 18 (Box A-821)
      - Wheeler Mental Health Clinic (Box A-821)
      - Whiting Forensic Institute (Box A-821)
  - Mental Retardation Office (Box A-821)
    - Correspondence A – Z (Box A-821)
    - Subject Files (Box A-822)
      - Auditors / OMR / John Dempsey Regional (Box A-822)
      - Autism, 1973 October 16 (Box A-822)
      - Autism Distinguished Service Awards (Box A-822)
      - Autism – Budget, 1974 (Box A-822)
      - Baldwin Bridge (Box A-822)
      - CARC Board Member, 1973 June 29 (Box A-822)
      - Central Ct. Regional Center (Box A-822)
      - Child Guidance (Box A-822)
      - Clinic (Box A-822)
      - Christmas Pageant, 1974 (Box A-822)
      - Contract for Services Analysis (Box A-822)
      - Danbury Regional Center (Box A-822)
      - Deinstitutionalization Brochure (Box A-822)
      - Dempsey Regional Center (Box A-822)
      - Development Disabilities (Box A-822)
      - Development Disabilities: State Planning & Advisory Council (Box A-822)
      - Draft Letter for OMR Pins (Box A-822)
      - Fairfield Regional Center (Box A-822)
      - Fairfield Regional Center, 1973 September 1 (Box A-822)
      - Form Letters Thank You / Governor's OMR Policy (Box A-822)
      - Foster Grandparents (Box A-822)
      - Fred Finn (Box A-822)
      - Governor’s Committee on Autism, 1973 September 28 (Box A-823)
      - Group Home Project (Box A-823)
      - Group Homes (Box A-823)
      - Growth, 1973 January (Box A-823)
      - Harkness Memorial (Box A-823)
      - Hartford Regional Center, 3 folders (Box A-823)
      - Land Grant from City of Bridgeport (Box A-823)
      - Long Range Plan (Box A-823)
      - Lower Fairfield Regional Center (Box A-823)
      - Lower Fairfield Regional County, 1974 January 31 (Box A-823)
      - Lower Fairfield Regional County, 1973 November 7 (Box A-823)
      - Lower Fairfield Regional County, Thank You Letters (Box A-823)
      - Mary Mansions (Box A-823)
      - Mental Retardation Council (Box A-823)
      - New Haven Regional Center (Box A-823)
      - North Central Regional (Box A-823)
      - People Who Have Written to the Governor (Box A-823)
      - Pamphlets, Info., etc. (Box A-823)
      - President's Council on Mental Retardation (Box A-823)
      - Printed Letter re 1974 Budget (Box A-823)
      - Project Challenge (Box A-823)
      - Project Challenge Flyers (Box A-823)
      - Project Challenge Legislature, 1974 January 24 (Box A-823)
      - Project Challenge, 1973 January 24 (Box A-823)
      - Project Place OMR (Box A-823)
      - Public Work Projects (Box A-823)
      - Regional Services Delivery Systems People and Programs (Box A-823)
      - Schmickel File (Box A-824)
      - Seaside Regional Center (Box A-824)
      - Southbury Training School (Box A-824)
      - Title 19 (Box A-824)
      - Varca (Box A-824)
      - Waterbury Regional Center (3 folders) (Box A-824)
  - Motor Vehicles Department (Box A-825)
    - Correspondence (Box A-825)
      - A – L (Box A-825)
      - M – Z (Box A-826)
    - Subject Files (Box A-827)
      - Accident Statistics (Box A-827)
      - Alcohol Programs (Box A-827)
      - Ansonia Branch Opening (Box A-827)
      - Branch Office Cost (Box A-827)
      - Centennial Marker Plates (Box A-827)
      - Chevrolets – 1965 Model Deficiencies (Box A-827)
      - Driver Education (Stanley Page File) (Box A-827)
      - Driver Education (Box A-827)
      - Drunk Driving (Box A-827)
      - Energy Crisis (Box A-827)
      - Fact Sheet (Box A-827)
      - Federal Legislation (Box A-827)
      - Federal State Clearing House (Grant Applications) (Box A-827)
      - Highway Safety Programs (Box A-827)
      - Info. from Com. Leuba (Box A-827)
      - Interoffice - from Leuba (Box A-827)
      - Labor Day Safety Message (Box A-828)
      - Legislation (Stanley Page’s Files) (Box A-828)
      - Legislation, 2 folders (Box A-828)
      - Lentini – Clemency, 1974 January 14 (Box A-828)
      - Licenses - Photo (Box A-828)
      - Memorial Day (Box A-828)
      - Miscellaneous (Stanley Page’s File) (Box A-828)
      - Motor Vehicle Institute (Box A-828)
      - Motorcycle Helmet Laws (Box A-828)
      - Motorcycles (2 folders) (Box A-828)
      - Noise Abatement (Box A-828)
      - Payroll Audit (Box A-828)
      - Payroll Audit Report, 1974 July 12 (Box A-828)
      - Plates (Box A-828)
      - Reflecting License Plates (Box A-828)
      - Safety Belts in State Vehicles (Box A-829)
      - Safety Commission (Box A-829)
      - Safety Kits (Box A-829)
      - Sale of Lists (Stanley Page’s File) (Box A-829)
      - School Bus Regulations (Box A-829)
      - Seat Belts, 2 folders (Box A-829)
      - Snowmobiles (Box A-829)
      - Spanish Manual (Box A-829)
      - Speaking Engagements Motor Vehicles (Box A-829)
      - Speed – Left-hand Lane (Stanley Page’s File) (Box A-829)
      - Speeding and Drunken Driving (S.P. File) (Box A-829)
      - Speeding Statistics (S.P. File) (Box A-829)
      - Stamford Branch (Box A-829)
      - State Ambulance Commission (S.P. File) (Box A-829)
      - State Owned Cards – Closed File (Box A-829)
      - State Owned Cards - Pending (Box A-829)
      - Torrington Branch Closing (Box A-829)
      - Traffic Safety School Course #71-1 (Box A-829)
      - Uniform Vehicle Registration (Box A-829)
      - Waterbury Branch Office (Box A-829)
  - Personnel Department (Box A-830)
    - Correspondence (Box A-830)
      - A – L (Box A-830)
      - M – Z (Box A-831)
    - Subject Files (Box A-832)
      - Audit (Box A-832)
      - Blood Donor Program (Box A-832)
      - Collective Bargaining, 2 folders (Box A-832)
      - Commissioner Pay Raise (Box A-832)
      - CSEA, 2 folders (Box A-832)
      - Defense Driver Course (Box A-832)
      - Emergency Employment Act (Box A-832)
      - Employee Relations Committee (Box A-832)
      - ERA (Box A-832)
      - Forty (40) Hour Week (Box A-832)
      - Hartford Courant Allegations (Box A-832)
      - Interoffice Memorandums (Box A-832)
      - Leave of Absences, Vacations & Vacancies (Box A-832)
      - Military (Box A-832)
      - PEP (Box A-832)
      - Pay Increases (Elected Officials) (Box A-832)
      - Pay Raise (Box A-832)
      - Pay Raise for State Employees (Box A-832)
      - Pay Raise (Box A-832)
      - Pay Raises for State Employees (Box A-832)
      - Personnel Appeal Board (Box A-832)
      - Personnel Suggestions (Box A-832)
      - Pre-Retirement (Box A-832)
      - Public Employment Relations (Box A-832)
      - Public Employment Relations Commis.(E.O.#11) (Box A-832)
      - Raynor, Ronald (Box A-832)
      - Salary (State Employees) (Box A-833)
      - Seaside Regional Center (Box A-833)
      - Speaking Engagements (Box A-833)
      - State Employees Cost of Living (Box A-833)
      - State Employees Pay Raises (Box A-833)
      - State Employees Salaries (Box A-833)
      - State Employees Speech Made by Com. Simpson (Box A-833)
      - State Employees Week (Box A-833)
      - State Personnel (Box A-833)
      - State Vehicles (Box A-833)
      - Training (Box A-833)
      - Tyler, Joe (Box A-833)
      - U – Wildey (Box A-833)
  - Public Utilities Commission (Box A-834)
    - General Correspondence (Box A-834)
    - Correspondence (Box A-835)
      - A – P (Box A-836)
      - Q – Z (Box A-836)
    - Subject Files (Box A-836)
      - Adj. (Non-payment) (Box A-836)
      - Adj. (Standard) (Box A-836)
      - Audit, 1974 June 25 (Box A-836)
      - Burnham’s Testimony (Box A-836)
      - Bozrah Light and Power (Box A-836)
      - Bridgeport Hydraulic (Box A-836)
      - Bus Crisis (Box A-836)
      - Citizens Groups (Box A-836)
      - Con Edison, 2 folders (Box A-836)
      - CL&P (Box A-836)
      - CL&P & HELCO (Box A-836)
      - Conn. Natural Gas, 4 folders (Box A-836)
      - Consultants / Refinery (Box A-836)
      - ”Continued Rise” (Box A-836)
      - Diorio (Box A-837)
      - Documents – PUC (Box A-837)
      - Federal Communications Comm. (Box A-837)
      - Fuel Cost Adjustment Mag. (Box A-837)
      - Fuel Cost Adjustment Follow Up (Box A-837)
      - Fuel Cost Petition (Box A-837)
      - Fuel Cost Petition / Short (Box A-837)
      - Fuel Cost Petition / Short, 1974 April 19 (Box A-837)
      - Gov. Meskill Agency Files (Box A-837)
      - Harlow (Box A-837)
      - HELCO (Box A-837)
      - HELCO & CL&P (Box A-837)
      - Legislation, 1975 (Box A-837)
      - Legislation, 2 folders (Box A-837)
      - Memos (Box A-837)
      - Miscellaneous & Publications (Box A-837)
      - NEEPS / Working Papers (Box A-837)
      - N.E. Energy Policy Staff (Box A-837)
      - N.E.P.O.O.L. (Box A-837)
      - New Haven Water Co. (Box A-837)
      - Northeast Utilities, 2 folders (Box A-837)
      - Northeast Utilities & Moody’s of all Utilities (Box A-837)
      - Northeast Utilities New Rate Increase, 1974 April (Box A-837)
      - Olmstead Water Co. (Box A-837)
      - Public Utilities Commission / Connecticut Company (Box A-838)
      - PUC Hearings (Box A-838)
      - Penn Central (Box A-838)
      - Petition to Intervene New Haven Water Company (Box A-838)
      - Press Releases (Box A-838)
      - Printed Letters Banking & Regulated Activities (Box A-838)
      - Printed Letters for PUC Petitions Signers, 1973 September 10 (Box A-838)
      - Printed Letters PUC TAP, 1974 February (Box A-838)
      - Public Intervenor (Box A-838)
      - PUC, 1974 April 29 (Box A-838)
      - PUC Dockets (Box A-838)
      - PUC Letters (Box A-838)
      - PUC Mag Letters (Box A-838)
      - PUC Miscellaneous (Box A-838)
      - Rate Hikes 1973 / Form Letters (Box A-838)
      - Rate Hikes HELCO - CL&P (Box A-838)
      - Rate Hikes Letters (Box A-838)
      - Rate Hikes / Post Testimony (Box A-838)
      - Rate Hike Request (Box A-838)
      - Rate Taxes & Approval (Support Letters) (Box A-838)
      - Repeal of Utility Tax, 1973 October (Box A-838)
      - Response to Tedesco Coupons (Box A-838)
      - Rules & Regulations (Box A-838)
      - Sales Tax on Utility (Box A-838)
      - Stamford Water Co. (Box A-838)
      - Southern Ct. Gas, 2 folders (Box A-838)
      - State Sales Day on PUC (Box A-838)
      - Stockholders Temporary Help (Box A-838)
      - Thank You / AARP, 1973 December 19 (Box A-838)
      - Truckers (Box A-838)
      - Trucking (Box A-838)
      - United Illuminating, 4 folders (Box A-838)
  - Public Works Department (Box A-839)
    - Correspondence A – Z (Box A-839)
    - General Correspondence (Box A-839)
    - Subject Files (Box A-839)
      - Announcement (Box A-839)
      - Appraised Property UConn (Box A-839)
      - Bidding Public Contracts (Box A-839)
      - Bridgeport Leasing, 1974 January (Box A-839)
      - Building Codes (Box A-839)
      - Building Codes Conference, 1973 May (Box A-839)
      - Central Naugatuck Center (Box A-839)
      - Commission on Demolition (Box A-839)
      - Community Correctional Center (Box A-839)
      - Deferred Projects (Box A-839)
      - Eastern Conn. State College (Box A-839)
      - Eastern Conn. Veterans Homes & Hospital (Box A-839)
      - Eastern Office (Box A-839)
      - Education Buildings (Box A-839)
      - Fact Sheets (Box A-839)
      - Fairfield County Regional Center (Box A-839)
      - Federal Govt. Legislation (Box A-839)
      - Governor Conference Room (Box A-839)
      - Groton Technical School (Box A-839)
      - Hartford Juvenile Court (Box A-840)
      - Hartford Regional Center (Box A-840)
      - Health Center (Box A-840)
      - Interoffice (Box A-840)
      - Lease (Box A-840)
      - Leases (Box A-840)
      - Leases - S. Page's File (Box A-840)
      - Leasing (Box A-840)
      - Leasing Fraud (Box A-840)
      - Legislation (Box A-840)
      - Manafort (Memos From) (Box A-840)
      - Memos from Biggs (Box A-840)
      - Memos to and from Com. Edward Kozlowski (Box A-840)
      - Miscellaneous (Box A-840)
      - Misc. Projects / S. Page (Box A-840)
      - Monthly Reports (Box A-840)
      - New Haven Correctional Center (Box A-840)
      - New London County Court House (Box A-840)
      - Norwich Hospital, 2 folders (Box A-840)
      - Press Releases (Box A-841)
      - Preston Court House (Box A-841)
      - Public Relations (Box A-841)
      - Public Safety-Commissioner (Box A-841)
      - Public Works Bi9ll 8857 Conn. Fire Marshall Assn. (Box A-841)
      - Public Works File - G. Allen (Box A-841)
      - Puerto Rican Population of New Haven (Box A-841)
      - Quarterly Report (Box A-841)
      - Silver Sands (Box A-841)
      - South Central (Box A-841)
      - South Central Public Works (Box A-841)
      - Space Allocation (Box A-841)
      - Speaking Engagements (Box A-841)
      - Stamford Court House (Box A-841)
      - State & Urban Development Committee on Public Works Leases, 1971-1972 (Box A-841)
      - State Land – Middletown Ct. Reverend Lorenzo Woods (Box A-841)
      - Supreme Court Building (Box A-841)
      - UConn Health Center (Box A-841)
      - UConn Med.-Dental Center (Box A-841)
      - Veterans Hospital Almquist (Box A-841)
      - Vinal Technical School (Box A-841)
      - Washington Office (Box A-841)
      - Waterbury Court House (Box A-841)
      - Waterbury Higher Education Complex (Box A-841)
      - Well Drilling Board (Box A-841)
      - Western Conn. State College, 2 folders (Box A-841)
  - Safety Commission (Box A-842)
  - Special Revenue Commission (Box A-843)
    - Correspondence A – Z (Box A-843)
    - Subject Files (Box A-844)
      - Anti-Lottery (Box A-844)
      - Anti-Gambling (Box A-844)
      - Commission on Special Revenue / Lottery (Box A-844)
      - Federal Legislation (Box A-844)
      - Gambling (Box A-844)
      - Horse Racing (Box A-844)
      - Lottery, 2 folders (Box A-844)
      - Lottery Line (Box A-844)
      - Memos to MacDonald (Box A-844)
      - Off Track Betting (Box A-844)
      - Racing (Box A-844)
      - Spanish-Speaking (Box A-844)
      - Spanish Speaking Fact Sheet (Box A-844)
      - Speaking Engagements (Box A-844)
      - Telegram - HR 6668 (Box A-844)
  - State Planning Office (Box A-845)
  - State Police (Box A-846)
    - Correspondence (Box A-846)
      - A – P (Box A-846)
      - Q – Z (Box A-847)
    - General Correspondence (Box A-847)
    - Subject Files (Box A-847)
      - Auditors Report/Norwalk State Police (Box A-847)
      - Auxiliary Graduates (Box A-847)
      - Babson College – Correctional Management Skills (Box A-847)
      - Checkmate (Box A-847)
      - Christmas Tree (Box A-847)
      - Conn. Fire Marshall (Box A-847)
      - Emergency Plan (Box A-847)
      - Feisal Folder (Box A-847)
      - Fire Advisory Council Fire Marshall (Box A-847)
      - Fire Prevention Letter (Box A-847)
      - Fuessenich - Normal State Technical (Box A-847)
      - Garner, David (Box A-847)
      - Garner, David – Rescue (Box A-847)
      - Governor’s Security Report (Box A-847)
      - Hot Dot (National Guard) (Box A-847)
      - Investigative Crime Task Force (Box A-847)
      - Japanese Ministers Visit (Box A-847)
      - Law Enforcement Manual (Box A-847)
      - List of Conn. Police Chiefs & Fire Chiefs (Box A-847)
      - Mail to and from Fuessenich (Box A-848)
      - Memorial Day Weekend (Box A-848)
      - Monthly Reports (Box A-848)
      - National Fire Academy (Box A-848)
      - Operation Checkmate (Box A-848)
      - Out-of-State Travel (Box A-848)
      - Pay Raise Letters (Box A-848)
      - Payroll Audit Report (Box A-848)
      - Motor Vehicles Statistics (Box A-848)
      - Pocket, Janice, 3 folders (Box A-848)
      - Police Promotions (Box A-848)
      - Regional & National Organizations / Travel & Participation (Box A-848)
      - Safety / Hot Dots (Box A-848)
      - Safety on the Streets (Box A-848)
      - Security Officer’s Reports (Box A-848)
      - State Police Letter (Box A-848)
      - State Police Reports (Box A-848)
      - State Police Speeding Statistics (Box A-848)
      - 357 Revolvers (Box A-848)
      - Trooper of the Year Award (Box A-848)
      - Wage Adjustments (Box A-848)
  - Tax Department (Box A-849)
    - Correspondence N – S (remainder missing) (Box A-849)
    - General Correspondence (Box A-850)
    - Subject Files (Box A-851)
      - Against Tax Program (Box A-851)
      - Amusement Tax (Box A-851)
      - Anti-Income Tax – Pro Sales Tax (Box A-851)
      - Anti-Real Estate Exchange Tax (Box A-851)
      - Articles from the Press (Box A-851)
      - Auditors Report (Box A-851)
      - Boating Fee (Box A-851)
      - Cabaret Taxes (Box A-851)
      - Capital Gains and Div. Form Letter (Box A-851)
      - Capital Gains – July (Box A-851)
      - Capital Gains Tax (Box A-851)
      - Cigarette Tax (Box A-851)
      - Cigarette Smuggling Legislation (Box A-851)
      - Circuit Breaker, 3 folders (Box A-851)
      - Circuit Breaker (Crouch Letter), 1973 December (Box A-851)
      - Circuit Breaker Fact Sheet (Box A-851)
      - Circuit Breaker Offset Letter (Box A-851)
      - Conveyance Tax, 2 folders (Box A-851)
      - Corporation Businesses (Box A-851)
      - Dividends Letter, 1973 July (Box A-851)
      - Dividends Refund Education (Box A-851)
      - Elderly (Box A-851)
      - Exemption Number (Box A-851)
      - Farms (Box A-851)
      - Form Letter (Dividends), 1973 July (Box A-851)
      - Form Letter Surplus (Box A-851)
      - Grants to Towns (Box A-851)
      - Hiring State Policemen (Box A-851)
      - Income Tax (Box A-851)
      - Inheritance Tax, 2 folders (Box A-851)
      - Job Vacancy (Box A-851)
      - Legislation, 2 folders (Box A-851)
      - Legislation, 1973 (Box A-851)
      - Licensing Fees Lawyers (Box A-851)
      - Liquor Tax (Box A-851)
      - Local (Box A-851)
      - Meal Tax, 2 folders (Box A-852)
      - Memorandums (Box A-852)
      - Non-Profit Organizations (Box A-852)
      - Out-of-State Tax (R.I. – N.Y.) (Box A-852)
      - Physicians Licensing Fees (Box A-852)
      - Pollution (Box A-852)
      - Printed Tax Letter, 1974 February (Box A-852)
      - Pro-Meskill Program - Taxes (Box A-852)
      - Property Taxes (Box A-852)
      - Publications (Box A-852)
      - Reduction Fact Sheet (Box A-852)
      - Registration Fees (Box A-852)
      - Response to Supporting Letters on Dividends (Box A-852)
      - Sales Taxes (Box A-852)
      - Sales Tax Letter Sent in Appreciation to State Auditors (Box A-852)
      - School Funding (Box A-852)
      - Speaking Engagements (Box A-852)
      - Speaking Engagements (F. George Brown) (Box A-852)
      - Tax Administrators News (Box A-852)
      - Tax Form Coupon A (Box A-852)
      - Tax Letters - No Addresses (Box A-852)
      - Tax Newsletter & Info. (Box A-852)
      - Taxes on Laundry (Box A-852)
      - Taxes - Thank-You for Support (Box A-852)
      - Tax on Dividends & Capital Gains (A-F) (Box A-853)
      - Tax on Dividends & Capital Gains (M-R) (Box A-853)
      - Tax Reform Commission (Box A-853)
      - Tax Refunds (Box A-853)
      - "Tax Review" (Box A-853)
      - Taxes and Tuition (Box A-853)
      - Taxes on Advertising (Box A-853)
      - Taxpayers Assn. Of Conn. (Box A-853)
      - Utility Tax (Box A-853)
      - Veterans Property Tax (Box A-853)
  - Transportation Department (Box A-854)
    - Correspondence (Box A-854)
    - Yellows (Box A-857a)
    - General Correspondence (Box A-858)
    - Subject Files (Box A-859)
      - Accident & Loss Prevention (Box A-859)
      - Advertising Schedule (Box A-859)
      - Aeronautics (General), 3 folders (Box A-859)
      - Aeronautics – Letters to Foreign Air Lines (Box A-859)
      - Air Pollution (Box A-859)
      - Air Line Hi-jacking (Box A-859)
      - Airports – State (Box A-859)
      - Allotments (Box A-859)
      - Allyn St. Connector, January-September (Box A-860)
      - AMTRAK (Box A-860)
      - Animal Export Center (Box A-860)
      - Ansonia Airport (Box A-860)
      - Appraisals (Box A-860)
      - Appreciation/Governor’s Trip to Bradley (Box A-860)
      - Aviation Federal Legislation (Box A-860)
      - Berkshire Line (Box A-860)
      - Bi-Weekly Status Report (Box A-860)
      - Bids (Box A-860)
      - Bike Grants (Box A-860)
      - Bluff (Box A-860)
      - Bolton Coventry Airport (Box A-860)
      - Bolton Coventry Airport (Form Letter) (Box A-860)
      - Bond Agenda (Box A-860)
      - Bond Com. (Box A-860)
      - Bradley Expansion (Box A-860)
      - Bradley Gateway, 3 folders (Box A-860)
      - Bradley International (Com. Wood's Trip to Europe) (Box A-861)
      - Bradley International Airport (Box A-861)
      - Bradley Post Office (Box A-861)
      - Brainard Airport (Box A-861)
      - Bridgeport Airport (Box A-861)
      - Bridges (Box A-861)
      - Brinegar (Box A-861)
      - Budd Car Conversion (Box A-861)
      - Budget – D.O.T. (Box A-861)
      - Budget Requests (Box A-861)
      - Buonome (Box A-861)
      - Bureau of Aeronautics Audit Report (Box A-861)
      - Burns (Box A-861)
      - Bus Capital Grants (Box A-862)
      - Bus Companies (Privately Owned) (Box A-862)
      - Bus Crisis (A-L) (Box A-862)
      - Bus Crisis (M-Z) (Box A-862)
      - Bus Crisis Folder (Box A-862)
      - Bus Form Letters (Box A-863)
      - Bus Legislation (Box A-863)
      - Bus Letters (Box A-863)
      - Bus Schedules (Box A-863)
      - Bus Service, 2 folders (Box A-863)
      - Bus Transit (Box A-863)
      - Buses (Box A-863)
      - Buses - Special Session Bushnell Connector (Box A-863)
      - Bushnell Park Connector (Box A-863)
      - Cab Hearings, 1974 June 11 (Box A-864)
      - Capital Grants (Box A-864)
      - Capitol Land Use Transportation (Box A-864)
      - Capitol Region Transportation Task Force (Box A-864)
      - Car Pooling, 5 folders (Box A-864)
      - Cargo Security (Box A-864)
      - Ceval (Box A-864)
      - Charted Air Travel (Box A-864)
      - Chester Hadlyme & Rocky Hill Ferry (Box A-864)
      - Civil Aeronautics Board (Box A-864)
      - Clam Digger (Box A-864)
      - Columbia (Box A-864)
      - Commuter / Conn. Turnpike Tickets (Box A-864)
      - Commuter Service (Box A-865)
      - Commuter Trains (Box A-865)
      - Concessions (Box A-865)
      - Congressional Record (Box A-865)
      - Conn. D.O.T. (Box A-865)
      - Connecticut Company (Box A-865)
      - Conn. D.O.T. Out of State (Box A-865)
      - Conn. – New York Modernization Program (Box A-865)
      - Conn. Safety Commission (Box A-865)
      - Conn. Transportation Authority (Box A-865)
      - Contract – CDOT (Box A-865)
      - Cornwall Bridge (Box A-865)
      - Cos Cob File (Box A-865)
      - Cos Cob Power Plant (Box A-865)
      - Council on Environmental Quality – 3221 – (Dale Van Winkle; Exec. Arr.=Huntington Williams) (Box A-865)